David L. Curry

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/dave-ls-curry/ **Email**: DaveCurry.email@gmail.com **Phone**: (206) 962-1161 **GitHub**: @LordSnoosh

I am a new software engineer in the process of a career change, who likes to look at the whole picture to find ways to develop a more intuitive user driven experience. Having a history of computer science and hardware technology, allows me to optimize my understanding of logical processes and statements that can translate to other coding languages. I have a strong sense of cooperation, and empathy, I think we all collectively want to succeed and we should all work towards that. I bring a fresh perspective to conventional thinking.

SKILLS

• Linux OS(ubuntu), HTML/CSS, JS, Node.js, Git, Express, Python, django, MongoDB, React, PostgreSQL, Heroku.

PROJECTS

- MiniMe Equipment A MERN stack app in continuous development for a fantasy shoppingcart.
- Spacecrafts Developed in a group setting, mirrors a vehicle trader site.
- Reflix Developed during a collabathon with the UXDI cohort at General Assembly.
- <u>Eberron Offerup</u> An Express app in the theme of D&D, one can manage mercenaries and adventures.

EXPERIENCE

Rairdon Subaru, Auburn, WA — Parts associate

2015 - 2021

- Assisted in catalog referencing, and parts inventory, along with managing repair tickets.
- Provided over the phone and over the counter service to customers and local repair shops.

Intellisoft LLC, Maple Valley, WA — Part Owner/Operator

2009 - 2011

- 2nd partner, and main technician for computer repair for over 3 years.
- Hired 2 employees and developed their skills as technicians.

ACS, Auburn, WA — Customer Service Rep

2008 - 2009

 Advanced customer service satisfaction, while providing over the phone technical troubleshooting.

EDUCATION

General Assembly, Online

May 2021

- Completed a 12-week, 480+ hour immersive Software Engineering program alongside other Engineers.
- Assisted in troubleshooting and support for other engineers, while completing required assignments.

Renton Technical College, Renton WA

2004-2005

- Studied and worked alongside other students to solve hardware and networking issues.
- Performed hands-on computer hardware and networking management in a closed network.

AWARDS & PERSONAL INTERESTS

- State-level awards for Speech & Debate resulting in a Letter
- Charitable work with St.Judes Children's Hospital
- Member Maple Valley Chamber of Commerce